new Stream platform I've seen Eh Eh Eh Eh Eh Eh Eh
nueva plataforma de Stream he visto Eh
Eh new
Eh Eh Eh Eh Eh Eh Eh nueva plataforma de
Stream platform new Stream platform I've
Stream nueva plataforma de Stream he
seen a rumor a rumor that I'm going to
visto un rumor un rumor de que voy a
open a streaming platform with
abrir una plataforma de streaming con
digref to start with no if I create a
digref para empezar no si creo una
streaming page I wouldn't give it a
página de streaming no le pondría un
name as [ __ ] crappy as the one that
nombre tan jodidamente cutre como el que
is rumored that it's going to be called it's called
se rumorea que se va a llamar se llama
dubi duap or something like that it's like what the [ __ ]
dubi duap o algo así es como qué [__]
is that bad name Eh bad name I don't know
es eso mal nombre Eh mal nombre no sé
who came up with that rumor but
quién se ha inventado ese rumor pero
believe me I
creedme que con esa [__] de nombre no
have nothing to do with that shitty name I have nothing to do with it It ca
tengo nada que ver No tengo nada que ver
n't be that the brand is true
No puede ser que que la marca sea verdad
the color is true that it's a
el color sea verdad que sea una
streaming platform okay It's not that they
plataforma de streaming vale No es que
lied to me it's that if they had lied to me
me hayan mentido es que si me hubieran
this would not exist directly
mentido no existiría esto directamente
but not apart from them telling me It's that
pero no aparte que me lo contaran Es que
I saw things that El Rubius and gref are going to be
yo vi cosas que El Rubius y gref van a
part of this in some way
ser partícipe de esto de alguna forma
Look are you ready for the future of
Mira estás listo para el futuro del
streaming Let's see who they
streaming A ver vamos a ver a quién
follow they only follow gref and Rubius
siguen siguen solo al gref y al Rubius
dude
tío